¿Sabes que?
This is crossing the line.
First, you kidnapped me,
then you dragged me here.
Now I have to pretend
to be your girlfriend.
Shh.
We had a deal.
No unnecessary questions.
Just bear with it longer.
Okay?
What?
Are you kidding me?
It's almost Christmas.
My next two weeks are
booked down to the hour.
Other people are depending
on me.
Do you even care about
anyone but yourself?
Stop talking.
Give me your hand.
Lymphoma means living
in constant fear.
I know what I'm talking about
as this disease has
knocked on my door too.
Michael.
What the hell is this now?
A non-disclosure agreement.
Just sign it if you want
your stuff back.
This will be a cutting-edge lab,
with the brightest minds
in modern medicine working here.
Yes, this year,
the Hendersons are playing Santa!
Let's keep believing in miracles.
You gave in quickly.
How much do I owe you?
I don't want a cent from you.
Just give me back my phone.
Michael.
Okay, bye.
What?
Is your fiancée
is leaving already?
Gina has business
to attend to, dad.
You like it when women
aren't just sitting at home
but actually working.
Gina, I expect to see you
at my house in a week.
I hope you don't work
on Christmas Eve?
Oh, actually, I don't-